Hello friends, I heartily congratulate you all.
Friends, the results of ICICI Bank have
come on 22nd January and ICICI
Bank also presents its results mostly on Saturdays. I will give you a
makeover of it. I have
not downloaded the results yet. Friends, I have
downloaded the fact sheet. I also have to give you some
more updates. If you want to know the results of two more stocks, then let's
start.
Friends, this is the fact sheet. Friends, you can
go to the bank's website and download it.
In the first point, you will see from this side,
2000% growth in core operating profit
because it is a good thing.
Deposit growth is also important for banks. If we go to the
current account savings account within the deposit group, then
you will see that the
average current account depositing and
33.70% near and savings account deposits have also
increased. On the front part 7, there is cent
higher oil and along with deposits, the
loan book is also important for banks. Loan
growth, so loans have also increased by 17.9%
on an annual basis and only
8.5%  Per cent growth has been shown on a quarterly basis.
Talking about retail loans, which is
important, they have also shown growth of 8.6 percent
on an annual basis and
they have jumped by 5.1 percent on a total basis
and their business banking portfolio has
also seen an increase of
30.78 percent, crop quarterly pulses and in such a case, there are
small medium enterprises, friends, and
semi small medium enterprises
portfolio has started growing by 34.2 percent
on an annual basis and they have shown growth on a daily basis of 98100, so after
looking at it, you must have got an idea, so the operating
profit can be calculated at 4.9 percent per annum.
You have shown hair growth, which is a
very good thing, operating profit is the main thing,
friends, without any judgment and
I told you that the income of banks comes
from interest, so after side effect adjustment,
their net interest income has increased by 20%,
currently it is 12236 and last
year in December quantity was 9912, so you
will see a good  Show the amount,
friends, in the net interest income there is
also a net interest margin, if the merchants
increase then they will benefit and they have
also shown an increase in the net interest margin,
it is 3.6 more and it has
also performed well in the earlier 3.67 margin
and friends, I
tell you that NDA and
provision are very important for banks, you will be
happy to know that their net NPA is across
and feels but I am talking about the temple here, it was
in numbers, it was
in quarterly room, 0.9, sure it is of December right now, that is the
contact method,
friends, you will see that 0.8 percent, there is a
decline on quarterly basis and on daily
basis there is a decline of 10 percent, so
this is a good thing, now as far as provision is concerned, friends,
in provision, friends,
they have performed well and
provision has been reduced by 2017 percent, the more difficult the NPA and
provision is
considered good for banks, how much provision have
they made now, it was in 2007 and before that it was last
year which was September 2003 scooter  Free 2742,
so you will see that a good tagline has come and the
provision and entry tax line is a
good sign for banks. Their standalone profit,
which has
come on a standalone basis, has grown by 20%.
And the concept is that friends, their
focus is completely on gas subsidy and there has been a
jump of 90% in it, that is, they have
increased the standalone and 20% profit after tax significantly.
And friends, I have
told you well about the bank earlier when it was around six hundred and fifty and it is worth noting that
they have
also shown growth in their digital payments and
their MP3 like activations which started with digital payments have happened
and the thing to note here is that
because these free like
activations have happened, these
activations have been done by people who did not have an ICICI Bank
account. So their app is a banking app,
anyone can download it. It does
not matter whether you have an ICICI
Bank account or not, anyone can
use it. So the number it is showing,
free like, it has shown that non
ICICI Bank account holders have
activated these for free
and used their digital services. Activation means they must have
downloaded an app from somewhere.
Friends, there has been an increase in UPI transactions. So,
that's a good sign. The bank has
performed very well. There's a decline in MP, there's a
decline in provisions,
and they've performed exceptionally well in net interest income. I keep
saying that anyone
who has a business bank should invest. There may be some
fluctuations today,
but there's nothing to worry about. They have
proven themselves, and the proof
can be seen in the results. Even after that,
they've done well. Friends,
this is an overview of the bank.
Now, we'll also look at the
results of two major insurance companies.
This is Gypsy's view. The share
price chart is plotted here.
Look here, friends, HDFC Life has been
in a limited range for a long time.
If any stop is within a limited range within several boxes, then
if a small piece of
good news comes for it, it
breaks the box and goes up. The
same reverse case is seen in this news.  It will go down and
it is also listed in 2017 and friends, the other
insurance company SBI Life, its
results have also come and you will see here
last Friday, certainly before being a market place,
first of all it had a tremendous spa
unit, which can be called the service of the result,
this is the answer to the result, both are big
companies, I have already told you about these two,
now
how did their results come, friends, I will also give a makeover of them, if I
tell you in retail then the video will become long,
friends, first of all I will talk about HDFC Life
Insurance, which, hello friends, the penetration is profit after
tax of 23.7
crores, so
3.3 percent of it is of assets, which is on a daily
basis, friends, like in banks there is net
interest income, which is called end-fire shot,
whereas in insurance companies there is
net premium income, that is, end-use
and how do insurance companies earn, from the
premium we disclose,
their net premium income has
grown by 27.8 percent, this is on this basis
and friends, mutual fund people and NDMC
and there are others in the insurance sector.  One thing is common,
event asset under management, that is,
how much money they have in Indore. The more
money there is to be managed, that means people are
taking more of their services because
more and more people will fill in, so the same
amount is called asset under management of choice
and so the current amount is
1.95 lakh crore, in which HDFC Life results have come down by 18 percent on a
regular basis.
Notepad Notepad I will make a note, the
front market did not like their results, so
friends, if we talk about SBI Life, then the
net profit of
SBI Life has come up to 36.46 percent for this, a mere
6% champion, if we
compare it with HDFC Life Insurance, then it has
performed very well and on this basis
and friends, their NPI, that is, net
premium income, has
increased by 30.39 percent
on an annual basis and if you keep it below the target, as
I told you, their net
premium income was 27.81 and theirs here is 30.39 percent
and now we will talk about asset under management,
how much money they have.  To manage
and the good amount they have
is 2.56 crores they have another amount
and suddenly Kunti friend has increased
friend oy friend on base and HDFC
Life had 1.95 lakh crores there
was an increase of 18% if we compare year to year then
Aishwarya's results have been better than HDFC Life
so friends out of both like this and
SBI Life has
performed well I would
say that friends if you
look at the quarter to quarter performance of insurance it was a little
bad, that is the reason I told you
I hope the results of SBI are
not bad the results of HDFC Life and I can say that it is
average I will
put it in the category of not good not made A grade you
can also call it flight results whoever has
strange life like SBI Life
ICICI Lombard keep them in mind
that the insurance sector friends has not started as much as it should have started in India
but if we talk about convention
and after the Beed Dal the awareness among the people has
increased that in future people will
definitely have insurance policy  They will
definitely take any Indian General Insurance
because awareness has increased, so
in the coming time the insurance sector will do well
and both HDFC Life and SBI Life are
part of the report, you should take your own decision on the basis of
its response in any decision,
while buying or selling any share or
booking profit, you should
take your own decision on the basis of previous studies, do not
invest in any stock based on hearsay
or in the greed of higher returns, if
you do some study and take time in the share market then
friends,
your returns will be easily made, for this you will have to be a
little patient, so friends, I hope
you liked the video,
stay healthy and happy, thank you very much